As you have just seen, indentation is important.
كما رأيتم للتو، فإن التحريك إلى مستوى أدنى مهم،
It's how we tell Python what code is in the body of an if statement,
وهي الطريقة التي نخبر بها Python بالكود الذي يقع داخل كتلة تعبير "if"،
and what code is outside of it.
وما هو الكود الذي يقع خارجها.
Indentation doesn't just matter in if statements.
التحريك إلى مستوى أدنى ليس مهماً في تعابير "if" فحسب.
Soon, you'll see it used in other contexts.
قريباً، سترون استخدامه في سياقات أخرى.
Some other languages use braces to show where blocks of code begin and end.
بعض اللغات الأخرى تستخدم الأقواس المتعرجة لبدء وإنهاء كتل الكود،
In Python, we use indentation to enclose blocks of code.
أما في Python، فنستخدم التحريك إلى مستوى أدنى لتحديد كتل الكود.
This indentation conventionally comes in multiples of four spaces.
التحريك إلى مستوى أدنى عادة ما يكون باستخدام مضاعفات أربع مسافات.
It's important to be strict about following this convention because
من المهم أن تكونوا صارمين في اتباع هذا العرف
changing the indentation can completely change the meaning of the code.
لأن تغيير مستوى المسافة البادئة بإمكانه أن يغير معنى الكود بالكامل.
If you are working on a team of Python programmers,
إذا كنتم تعملون ضمن فريق من مبرمجي Python،
it's important that everyone follows the same indentation convention.
فمن المهم أن يتبع الجميع مستوى المسافة البادئة المتفق عليه ذاته.